<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on madmx</title>
        <link>/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on madmx</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 20:53:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Shelter in Place</title>
            <link>/posts/shelter-in-place/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 20:53:50 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>/posts/shelter-in-place/</guid>
            <description>I come from Quebec, Canada. I spent most of my life in the outdoors, or at least free to go take a stroll. Never in my life have I thought I would be strongly encouraged to stick within our 4 walls in Harlem. Never in my life have I stayed a whole week inside.
The family is adjusting. Working feels different. No commute or going outside for lunch. Removing the physical distance of the office requires us to enforce our own schedule so we don&amp;rsquo;t over work.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I come from Quebec, Canada. I spent most of my life in the outdoors, or at least free to go take a stroll. Never in my life have I thought I would be strongly encouraged to stick within our 4 walls in Harlem. Never in my life have I stayed a whole week inside.</p>
<p>The family is adjusting. Working feels different. No commute or going outside for lunch. Removing the physical distance of the office requires us to enforce our own schedule so we don&rsquo;t over work.</p>
<p>Yet here we are, in 2020. This uninvinted virus has come to our door. Invisible, odorless, and ready to infect anyone in its way. Especially older folks, who ironically went through similar distressing times.</p>
<p>We already see reports of members of our community pass away, and I really hope it won&rsquo;t hit closer to home.</p>
<p>On the brighter side, we do have good things coming our way, so there is a silverlining in these uncertain times.</p>
<p>And with all that extra time, I figured I might as well start writing again. I&rsquo;ve never been great at consistently updating a blog, but I have to start somewhere?</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
